# CHIGOZIE MUONAGOLU

54 Hilliard Street · 6472251047 Cmuonagolu18@gmail.com

Hi,

My name is Chigozie Muonagolu, and I am an international student from Nigeria. Currently, I am trying to achieve my Honors Bachelor's degree in Computer Science with the goal of specializing in Software Engineering. A little bit about myself, I am a very reliable and honest person and, also a very hardworking person who is always ready to face the challenges thrown at me.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

JULY 2018 - NOVEMBER 2018: 3 MONTHS
SALES ASSOCIATE, RICHBON GROUP LIMITED

The roles included:

- Taking inventory count every day when the shop opened up.
- Lifting products up to 50 lbs.
- Getting customers' orders and completing the sales.
- Assisting in restocking the shop.

OCTOBER 2019 - APRIL 2020: 7 MONTHS LINE COOK, TERRY'S PLACE

The roles included:

- Making sure the kitchen was set up properly.
- Keeping inventory of the food in storage and restocking them.
- Cleaning up after prepping meals.

#### **EDUCATION**

**SEPTEMBER 2020 TILL DECEMEBER 2023** 

**BACHELOR'S DEGREE IN COMPUTER SCIENCE, TRENT UNIVERSITY** 

**SEPTEMBER 2019 TO APRIL 2020** 

BACHELOR'S DEGREE IN COMPUTER SCIENCE, NIPPISSING UNIVERSITY

JANUARY 2019 TO JULY 2019
HIGH SCHOOL DIPLOMA, VINERIDGE ACADEMY

## **SKILLS**

- Hardworking and willing to take on challenges.
- Quick, Critical thinker and a problem solver.
- Great teamwork skills.
- Very dependable and honest.
- Always eager to learn.

### **VOLUNTEER EXPERIENCE**

January 2019 | Vineridge Academy
Part of cleanup crew for the Niagara Ice wine festival
Niagara-On-The-Lake, Ontario

March 2019 | Vineridge Academy Spring Clean up Niagara-On-The-Lake, Ontario

July 2019 | Vineridge Academy Volunteered to help serve cake on Canada day Niagara-On-The-Lake, Ontario